{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is the generic block HTML tag that acts as a container to organize portions of code?",
            "options": [
                "<span>",
                "<p>",
                "<div>",
                "<a>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which attribute does an img tag need to help people using screenreaders?",
            "options": [
                "alt",
                "href",
                "height",
                "width"
            ],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is the meta tag located in the HTML document?",
            "options": [
                "<body>",
                "<style>",
                "<script>",
                "<head>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which attribute on a HTML element allows a tooltip about the element to be displayed?",
            "options": [
                "alt",
                "style",
                "title",
                "src"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which attribute allows the elements of a table to span multiple columns ?",
            "options": [
                "col",
                "colgroup",
                "rowspan",
                "colspan"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "How is a hyperlink from an <a> element opened in an <iframe> element on the same webpage ?",
            "options": [
                "Adding an id attribute to the iframe and using it as the value of the target attribute of the a tag element.",
                "Adding a name attribute to the iframe and using it as the value of the target attribute of the a tag.",
                "Changing the target attribute value of the a tag element to _blank",
                "Forget it, you can't open links on the same webpage as the <a> element."
            ],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are semantic HTML elements important?",
            "options": [
                "They help search engines and other user devices to determine importance and context in a webpage.",
                "They are shorter to type out.",
                "They make the internet more colourful.",
                "They allow you to use HTML in the python programming language."
            ],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "What are HTML description lists commonly used for?",
            "options": [
                "To display the styles of the webpage.",
                "To implement a glossary or to display metadata(a list of key-value pairs).",
                "To separate <ul> and <ol> tags.",
                "To display images."
            ],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which element defines an HTML dropdown list?",
            "options": [
                "<p>",
                "<textarea>",
                "<input>",
                "<select>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which element in the head of the HTML document makes the webpage responsive?",
            "options": [
                "<meta charset=UTF-8 />",
                "<meta name=viewport content=width=device-width, initial-scale=1 />",
                "<link rel=stylesheet href=styles.css />",
                "<title>Document</title>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which tag allows characters to be displayed in a bold font?",
            "options": [
                "<code>",
                "<abbr>",
                "<i>",
                "<strong>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which audio attribute allows an audio file to play automatically?",
            "options": [
                "<audio src=audio.mp3 playnow></audio>",
                "<audio src=audio.mp3 autoplay></audio>",
                "<audio src=audio.mp3 loop></audio>",
                "<audio src=audio.mp3 controls></audio>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 1,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the <pre> HTML element used for?",
            "options": [
                "It represents a preformatted text that should be rendered how it is written in the HTML file.",
                "An alternative to the <p> tag",
                "Helps the prettier code formatter work more efficiently.",
                "To precede the <hr> tag."
            ],
            "correctOption": 0,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which HTML character entity represents a non-breaking space?",
            "options": [
                "&buy;",
                "&pound;",
                "&reg;",
                "&nbsp;"
            ],
            "correctOption": 3,
            "points": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "Which semantic HTML tag represents a navigation bar?",
            "options": [
                "<navigation>",
                "<div>",
                "<nav>",
                "<navbar>"
            ],
            "correctOption": 2,
            "points": 10
        }
    ]
}